clegent.com 2014-03-12

# Privacy Policy: SEO Services & PPC Campaign Management Company | Clegent™ Online Marketing Company

The information you place on clegent.com, we understand the value of that, that’s why we care for highest standards of security for the privacy of transaction and customer information.

Please read following statements to know about our privacy policy (these policies are subject to change time to time without informing to anyone, so please keep updated with these).

Whenever you signup free account on clegent.com, we collect your personal information like email address, name, phone number, etc. We do use your contact information to inform you related to offers on the products you purchased previously or are related to your interest. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law.

We use your person information submitted to clegent.com while registering an account, to market you our products and we will provide you the ability to opt-out from such uses. When you visit clegent.com (even if you do not register with clegent.com), we collect your machine IP address, browser, URL you came from, domain types, the pages of our website you visited, your location, the advertisements you clicked on, etc. This data helps us to improve us to serve you better ways. 

We use third-party banners or other advertisements on our website and these websites can gather information (not personal information like name, email id) about your visit to our website to improve their advertisement related to your interest.
